# **OLORUNBUNMI OLAJUMOKE**

@ ob.sharonnie@gmail.com

#### SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated computer science graduate from Yaba college of Education, seeking a mobile application development internship position. With close to 5 years' experience in web design and development, I have an excellent working knowledge of html, css and JavaScript. I seek to join a dynamic team where I can utilize and enhance my practical knowledge and my skills to help drive the success of the organization. I am known for my attention to details and excellent communication skills.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Graphic Designer**

#### Freelancer

🛱 07/2018 - Present

Location

Company Description

- · Produced creative designs using photoshop and coreldraw
- Retouch Images
- Prepare and Create artwork
- · Worked on logos, fliers and calender designs
- · Made sure deeadlines where met
- · Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

#### Frontend Developer

#### **RAACB**

**=** 03/2018 - 08/2018

Location

Company Description

- Created print and web graphics, banners, landing pages, and webpages
- Design User Interfaces across all platforms
- · Work with backend developers to create web applications
- created company offical website

## Front Desk Receptionist

#### HiiT PLC

**=** 02/2017 - 05/2017

Location

HiiT is a IT training company in ikeja

- · Checked clients in and out
- Maintained vistors and staff logs
- · Collected detailed information from vistors and clients
- · Recieving training in web design for the duration siwes

## **EDUCATION**

# **HND** in Computer Science

#### Yaba College of Technology

**ii** 06/2021 - 02/2023 **♀** Location

· Completed 2 years duration of study with a CGPA of 2.87/4

#### **SKILLS**

HTML CSS

SS JavaScript

PHP

**MS Office** 

**Adobe Photoshop** 

Bootstrap

## **STRENGTHS**



#### **Communication**

I have learnt that only through the right manner of communication can someone become better at the work



#### Teamwork

Having worked in a team before i have learnt to adapt my style of work into my team members and vice versa



#### Creativity

I have been faced with problem which at first glace are unsolvable, learnt the only way to tackle is to think outside the box and ask the right question



#### Multitasking

Aside from always planning my week ahead, i have developed a keen habit of multitasking in order to meet up deadlines

# **TRAINING / COURSES**

#### **Mobile Web Specialist**

Google Africa Developer Scholarship

# **Web Design**

HiiT Training Center

#### **HOBBIES**



Reading Books (both fictional and non fictional



**Digital Art** 

## **LANGUAGES**

**English** Native

